

**\( +1 437 556 3650** 

yuenting3328@gmail.com

https://portfolio--melodytse.netlify.app/#/

### **ABOUT ME**

Hi! I'm Melody Tse and I am a UX/UI Designer currently based in Toronto. With over 3 years of experience in digital projects based in Hong Kong,

I am driven to create digital products and websites that meet both business objectives and human needs.

# **EDUCATION**

# **Hong Kong Baptist University**

Bachelor of Arts (Hons.) in Visual Arts 2019

First Class Honour, Dean's List

Scholastic Award for Bachelor of Arts (Hons.) in Visual Arts

# **SKILLS**

# **Design Skills**

Product Design UX/UI Design
Branding & Identity Wireframe
User Research User Flow
Prototyping Testing

Visual Design Responsive Design

Video Editing

### **Design Tools**

Figma Sketch

Adobe XD Adobe Illustrator

Adobe InDesign Adobe Photoshop

Final Cut Pro Spine

# Development

JavaScript HTML/CSS ReactJS
Github MUI Ant Design

#### **EXPERIENCE**

Sep Jun 2022 - 2023

# **UX/UI Designer**

Automated Systems (H.K.) Limited - Hong Kong

#### WINGS e-IP | SFC

Led the project's design aspect, followed design thinking methodology for streamlined processes.

Worked closely with the Business Analysis team to determine ways to attain business goal and analyse users' need.

Translated concepts and user requirements in user flows and wireframes that resulted in an intuitive user experience.

Created UI library and styles in Figma, to align the styles across the files, maintain designs systematically at scale and enhance efficiency.

Validated design solutions by conducting a soft consolidation workshop with the user to review high-fidelity prototypes.

Apr Aug 2021 - 2022

# **Solution Developer (UX/UI Designer)**

PCCW Solutions Limited - Hong Kong

### eMPF Platform | MPFA

Collaborated with design and development teams to design and customize a one-stop MPF platform, serving 4.7 million members and 300,000 employers.

Utilized React.js and MUI Library to tailor front-end components and portal themes.

#### Next Generation Licensing Platform | SFC

On-site creation and revamp of app, responsive web platforms and internal system directly with customers.

Worked closely with product owners, developers and business analysis to define product requirements and solutions.

Led video designers and developers working with post-production tasks for fulfil the tight schedule.

#### HA Go | Hospital Authority

Improved the Invited Carer feature of the meditation app resulting in a 3.6-star rating and 5.97K reviews on Google Play.

Identified design problems, performed research to enable quality solutions that met user expectations.

Jan Mar 2020 - 2021

### **Graphic Designer**

Motic Hong Kong Limited - Hong Kong

Designed various packages, brochures, logos, and style guides to be used in stores and catalogs internationally.

Created user interface and web-based applications using a variety of tools and technologies, including HTML, CSS, Shopify and Magento.